ridester.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy – Ridester

**Ridester.com**

**Privacy Policy**

**Effective Date: December 7, 2018**

This Privacy Policy (“ **Policy** ”) describes how Rethink402, LLC (“ **Company** ”, “ **us** ”, “ **our** ”, and “ **we** ”) collects, uses and shares information from and about users of its website https://www.ridester.com/ (the “ **Site** ”).  This Policy also describes the measures that Company takes to protect the information, your options for choice and access, and how you can contact us about privacy practices.  This Policy is part of our Terms of Use (the “ **Terms** ”) for the Site. By using the Site, you acknowledge you have read and accept this Privacy Policy.

  1. **What We Collect**

1.1 “ **Personal Information** ”, as used in this Policy, is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable person.  We collect Personal Information from you in the following ways: 

We collect Personal Information when you submit it to us, including when you ask to be added to our mailing list, contact us through the Site, participate in a community forum, create an account through our Site or otherwise directly give it to us, by email or otherwise.  The Personal Information you submit may include your name, email address, username, and affiliated website.

We may also, to the extent permitted by applicable law, receive Personal Information about you from third parties including social media services or other commercially available sources. The Personal Information we receive from third parties may include your name, contact information, information about your transactions, relationships with product and service providers, and your use of certain applications. For example, if you access our Site through a social media service or connect our Site to a social media service, we may collect your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service and any information the social media service shares with us, such as your profile picture or email address. The information we obtain depends on your privacy settings on the applicable social media service. When you access the Site through social media services or when you connect our Site to social media services, you are authorizing us to collect, store, and use such information in compliance with this Policy.

1.2 “ **Other Information** ”, as used in this Policy, is any information that is not intended to disclose your specific identity to us, such as usage data, browser information, information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies, demographic information, geolocation data obtained with your consent where required by applicable law, and aggregated data. We collect Other Information from you in the following ways: 

We collect Other Information when you submit it to us. This may include your password or other information, such as your birthday or occupation, that you voluntarily provide to us through the Site. 

We may receive Other Information about you from third parties, including, for example, demographic data, social media account number, information about your interests or information about your activities on other websites.

We and our service providers may automatically collect information through cookies and other tracking technologies (collectively “ **Cookies** ”) when you visit our Site to provide and improve the Site, and to display relevant content, products, services and advertising.  Through the use of Cookies, we may obtain information about your computer or device, including computer operating system type and device characteristics, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, and the name of your Internet service provider, and your activities, including the website you visited before browsing our Site, pages you viewed, how long you spent on a page, the number and frequency of your visits, access times, and other information about your use of and actions on our Site.

  2. **How We Use Your Information**

We may use your Personal Information for the purposes set forth below.  We may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose; provided that if such Other Information is considered Personal Information under applicable law or if we combine Other Information with your Personal Information, we will treat such information as Personal Information.

2.1 Use of Cookies  

Third parties, such as analytics providers, ad networks, and advertisers, may use Cookies to track your online activities over time and across third party websites, apps and devices.  We may not have access to these Cookies, but we may use information obtained through the use of these Cookies to improve our products and services.  The information we obtain through these Cookies, along with Personal Information and Other Information we collect from your use of the Site (including through use of any Cookies that we employ to collect information from our Site), can be used to help improve our content, remember your preferences, personalize offerings, and show you advertisements that may be tailored to your interests.   These third party companies may also transfer this information to other parties where required to do so by law, or where such other parties process the information on their behalf.   

Specifically, we and our service providers may use advertising Cookies to deliver ads that we think will be relevant to you and your interests.  We may use advertising Cookies to customize the advertising and content you receive on our Site, conduct interest-based advertising, limit the number of times you see the same ad on our Site, help measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns, and conduct market research. These Cookies remember what you have looked at or purchased on our Site and other sites, and may be combined with other information acquired from third parties such as demographics and other marketing information.  We may share this information with other organizations, such as advertisers, in accordance with applicable law.  Third party advertisers and other organizations may also use their own Cookies to collect information about your activities on our Site and/or the advertisements you have clicked on. This information, which may be combined with other marketing information acquired from third parties, may be used to provide advertisements on our Site and third party sites that they think will be of interest to you based on content you have viewed. Third party advertisers may also use this information to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to track aggregate usage statistics. 

We are not responsible for any third-party websites, apps, advertisements, content or special offers linked or referenced on our Site.  We do not control any Cookies or other similar devices placed on our Site by third parties, such as those that may be embedded in third-party advertising.  We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.  Once you leave our Site or click an advertisement, or sign up for a special offer, the applicable third party privacy policy will apply.  

2.2 To Provide Content and to Operate, Maintain and Improve Our Site

We use Personal Information and Other Information we collect from and about you to operate, maintain, and improve our Site, including to (i) deliver the content, products and services offered through our Site or that users request, (ii) to create and manage your accounts, and (iii) allow you to engage with us (e.g., to comment on content or send us Feedback (as defined in the Terms).  We may also use the information we collect from you to analyze website use and improve and customize the content, layout, and services of our Site.  

2.3 To Provide (and Allow Third Parties to Provide) Advertising and Interest-Based Advertising 

We and our service providers may use any of the information we collect from and about you to allow us to provide ads about products and services tailored to your individual interests when you use our Site. We may work with third party advertising companies, advertisers and ad networks who help deliver these ads to you. These third parties may collect and use information about your activities on our Site and on other websites to provide ads to you that are believed to be consistent with your interests.  Please see additional details in Section 2.1 above.

2.4 To Allow Social Sharing Functionality 

If you log in with, or connect a social media service account to, our Site, we may use Personal Information and Other Information to facilitate your sharing of information between our Site and your social media service.

2.5 To Contact You 

We may send you materials about promotions, upcoming events, and other news related to the content offered on our Site and products and services from our selected partners. We may use and combine any of the Personal Information and Other Information we collect to assist us in sending you these materials. We may also contact you to respond to your comments, questions, requests or other Feedback and to provide customer service.  

2.6 To Protect Our Rights and the Rights of Others 

We may use your Personal Information, as we find necessary or appropriate in our discretion, and as permitted by law to: resolve disputes or troubleshoot problems; comply with law and respond to lawful requests from public and government authorities and legal processes; protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of Company or its employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements, policies and Terms); protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of our Site or other third parties; enforce contractual and intellectual property rights; and protect against fraud and other unlawful activity or for risk management purposes.

  3. **How We Share Your Information**

3.1 Our Disclosure of Personal Information and Other Information

3.1.1 To Allow Third-Party Service Providers to Help Us Operate Our Site 

We may provide your Personal Information to third party service providers who help us operate our Site, by, for example: developing or supporting content, products and features; sending email messages on our behalf; processing data or statistics; and serving, customizing or delivering marketing. These third party service providers are required to protect Personal Information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific service they are providing on our behalf.

3.1.2 To Allow Social Sharing Functionality

If you log in with, or connect a social media service account to, our Site, you are authorizing us to share information we collect from and about you with the social media service provider, and you acknowledge that the use of such information by the social media service will be governed by its privacy policy. If you do not want your Personal Information shared in this way, please do not connect your social media service account with our Site, and do not participate in social sharing on the Site.

3.1.3 To Protect Our Rights or the Rights of Others 

There may be instances when we may disclose your Personal Information, including situations where we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: comply with law and respond to requests from public and government authorities and legal processes; protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of Company or its employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements, policies and Terms); protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of our Site or other third parties; enforce contractual and intellectual property rights; and protect against fraud and other unlawful activity or for risk management purposes, to the extent permitted by applicable law.

3.1.4 In the Case of a Merger, Sale of Assets or Bankruptcy

If we sell all or part of our business or assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger, reorganization, dissolution, liquidation, or other transfer of all or part of our business or assets, we may transfer your information to the party or parties and their advisors involved in that transaction.

3.2 Information You Make Public through Use of Our Site 

Certain features on our Site, including community forums or comment posting features, give you an opportunity to interact with us and others. When you use these features, any information you choose to submit, including the information requested from you in order to participate in such feature and the information included in your post, may be publicly available to anyone, including other users, search engines, advertisers, and anyone else with access to the Site. We are not responsible for any information you choose to submit and make public through these interactive features.

  4. **How We Protect Personal Information**

We use reasonable measures to safeguard Personal Information.  However, no one can guarantee the complete safety of your information.  You acknowledge and agree that the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through the Site cannot be guaranteed and that you use the Site and send us information at your own risk.  If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please contact us immediately at the address below.

  5. **Your Rights and Choices**

5.1 Opt Out of Direct Marketing 

You may opt out of receiving electronic communications from us (including our newsletter or promotions), by contacting us at the address provided below or following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  Please note that there are certain service notifications that you may not opt out of, such as notifications of changes to your account. 

5.2 Opt Out of Interest-Based Advertising

You may opt out of online interest-based advertising by taking the steps detailed below. 

By using the Site with your browser setting adjusted to accept Cookies, you consent to the use of Cookies by us, our service providers and advertisers as set forth in this Policy.  Many browsers are set to accept Cookies until you change your settings.  You can remove and reject cookies from our Site through your browser settings. Most browsers will tell you how to change your browser settings to notify you when a Cookie is being set or updated, or to restrict or block certain types or all Cookies. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information.  Your device settings may also allow you to prohibit mobile app platforms from sharing certain information obtained by automatic processes with us.  

Advertising Cookies on our Site include Google Adsense.  For further information, including how to opt out, please see: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/).   

Analytics Cookies on our Site include Google Analytics.  For further information, including how to opt out, please see: [https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html](https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

Opting out of advertising Cookies does not remove advertising from our Site; instead it means the ads you will see may not be matched to your interests.

If you make updates to your browser or device settings, or use an online link to opt out of Cookies, those updates apply to the device where you made the changes. Please note that disabling or blocking Cookies could affect how certain functions on our Site work for you.

5.3 How to Access, Correct, Update or Delete Your Personal Information

You can access, correct, update or delete your Personal Information by contacting us at the address below. You can also object to or restrict the processing of your Personal Information. You can also exercise any rights you are entitled to under law. 

Where you have provided your consent to our use of your Personal Information, you can withdraw your consent and we will apply your preferences going forward.  We may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions you began prior to requesting such change or deletion.

5.4 California Privacy Rights

Subject to certain limitations, California Law permits users who are California residents to request certain information regarding disclosure of Personal Information during the preceding calendar year to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, California residents can write to us at the address set forth below.  Please include your name and the address to which you would like us to respond.

  6. **Other Important Information**

6.1 Updates to Privacy Policy

This Policy is effective as of the Effective Date set forth above. We have the right to change or update this Policy at our discretion and without notice to you.  This Policy is subject to occasional revision and, if we make any material changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our Site indicating we have updated this Policy.  Continued use of our Site following these changes means you acknowledge you have read and accept the revised Policy. 

6.2 Do Not Track Disclosure 

Some browsers or other tools include “Do Not Track” (DNT) features which, when turned on, send a signal to websites you visit indicating you do not wish to be tracked across websites over time.  We do not currently respond to DNT signals. 

6.3 Children Under 13

Our Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any Personal Information to or on the Site. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use this Site or provide any information on this Site. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at the address below.

  7. **Contact Us**

We welcome your comments or questions about this Policy. You may contact us at our address:

Rethink402, LLC 

Attn:  Privacy Policy Department

PO Box 541028

Omaha, NE 68116

Email: info@ridester.com

Please do not disclose any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs or health, social security numbers, or criminal background information) when contacting us.
